Opening.
I have recently started filming a drama series, and I have to go out once a month or so.
I was really worried,
I was really worried. But as for Monomurai, there is nothing I can do because of this situation.
I have been cast as the lead in a drama that will become a monthly drama, and now the question of what I will do if I get the lead role in Monomurai has come up,
There is a large number of people who are not yet ready to become monomaniacs, but there is a large number of people in the Nominee reserve army.
What? Where?
Oh, they're all over the place.
Behind the eyelids?
There are a lot of them in the lower age brackets and above, and I'm trying hard not to become one.
But there are a lot of preppers, and what if they do?
But what if they do? It's like they bumped into each other somewhere.
But then the connection might be lost or something.
I think this is a big problem, and if it really happens, it's really not funny.
I think it's a big problem, and if it really happens, it's really not funny.
Not a single person said anything. No one said anything. They don't know anything.
I really want to go to a training camp with Iwakai. Not a single person said anything. I don't know anything about it.
I really want to go to a camp with Iwakai.
Training camp with Iwakai?
Why would you want to do that?
Iwaumi, no matter what I do, you mustn't eat that. If you eat it, you can do it again,
I want to go to a camp with Iwaumi.
Why do you want to go to a training camp?
Because you are that passionate about the drama.
That is true.
I want to make it a day of exhaustive virtue.
Gunkite camp?
I want to talk with gankites forever.
Aren't you tired? Are you stressed out?
Not at all. I'm totally fine.Not at all. I'm totally fine.
I feel like an angel.
Watch out, watch out. This type is the most dangerous.
He's hoarding.
There's something I've always wanted to do,
I want to disguise myself like a celebrity.
Like the people who are often captured in weekly magazines.
I'm wearing sunglasses, I'm there, I'm wearing a hat,
I'm wearing a hat, and I've got my e-pants on here,
I'm not wearing sunglasses.
I'm wearing thin sunglasses,
The sunglasses are big enough to see through my eyes.
I am wearing sunglasses.
This is me looking at you.
I'm being photographed from around there.
It's like I'm wearing a cassock or something like that.
Highly sensitive actress type?
Highly sensitive actress type.
The Bakehawa idol.
She looks like an artist.
I don't know if she's fashionable or what, and people around her can't say anything.
What do you actually wear when you walk around?
I've never been approached by anyone with that...no...no one will ever know...really no one will know...this is a winner for sure!
Free streaming on t-bar until Oct. 2!
Now through October 2nd.
I'm thinking about what genre of person I would like to offer the next one, maybe Sakura-chan. I thought, "I'd like to have a day of defeat like Sakura-chan.
So, someone who is more brazen and brazen,
I'd like someone who can't read the air.I'd like someone who doesn't seem to be able to read the air on anything.
It's harder to make an offer.
The next person who came.
That's, so I won't say who.
So, I saw the next person on the VTR, and the staff did this.
It's not fair.
But still, the best part of this project is that it really makes everyone smile, and that makes me happy,
They say things like, "Thanks to Kyokolohi, we were able to have such fun.
That makes me happy.
What about the kids who just graduated from idol shows?
That's good.
The ones who have just graduated from idol shows, who have a thick-skinned look.
I don't want that. Anyone.
I'm happy with anyone.
I wanted to wish Saito-san a happy birthday.
Please do.
Wow! Yay! I'm so happy! I'm so happy! I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
Shaved ice!
I'm happy! I'm happy! I'm so happy!
Are you okay? Takeuchi?
Thank you very much.
This is so genius!
Congratulations!
You're 27? I am 26.
What are your ambitions for 26?
At 26, I have a strong desire to work hard in acting,
I hope to do my best in acting as much as Hikorohi does.
Follow me.
Thank you very much.
Where did you get this?Where is this from?
It's the one closest to Lokongi, by the way.
By the way, I can make matcha, mango, strawberry and tiramisu now.
Tiramisu is so good.
I want to eat tiramisu. I want to eat tiramisu.
Wow, that's great.
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
-Did you just make this? -oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, I'm so happy. Oh, my God.
Yeah!
How did you first get hooked?
A member took me out and I was hooked.
Is it totally different from regular hard ones?
That's why I like it so much.
Takeuchi Kakihyo Club.
I know it's a little embarrassing.
TakeuchiThe Kaki-Hyori Club is right on your heels.
Does it feel like it's melting? You mean it's not too crunchy?
Yes, it does. It turns into an ocean at the end.
It's a little too happy. It turns into an ocean.
That's the point. No, you can't try to cover it up.
I always say that.
Like, "I'm the ocean again.
Also, my tongue is getting really stuck. It's surprisingly hard to roll my tongue down there. I didn't know it was like this. All the time. That's enough, that's enough.
I'm talking to you.
It's true. You.